<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>markdown on banksy</title><link>https://banksy10.github.io/tags/markdown/</link><description>Recent content in markdown on banksy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://banksy10.github.io/tags/markdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>光线追踪</title><link>https://banksy10.github.io/ray-tracing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://banksy10.github.io/ray-tracing/</guid><description>概述 光线追踪（英语：ray tracing）是三维计算机图形学中的特殊渲染算法，跟踪从眼睛发出的光线而不是光源发出的光线，通过这样一项技术生成编排好的场景的数学模型显现出来。这样得到的结果类似于光线投射与扫描线渲染方法的结果，但是这种方法有更好的光学效果，例如对于反射与折射有更准确的模拟效果，并且效率非常高，所以当追求高质量的效果时经常使用这种方法。----维基百科 Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).
Paragraph There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.</description></item><item><title>测试2</title><link>https://banksy10.github.io/test-d/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://banksy10.github.io/test-d/</guid><description>Text Text can be **bold**, _italic_, or ~~strikethrough~~. [Links](https://github.com) should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over). Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).
Paragraph There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.</description></item><item><title>测试3</title><link>https://banksy10.github.io/test-f/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://banksy10.github.io/test-f/</guid><description>Text Text can be **bold**, _italic_, or ~~strikethrough~~. [Links](https://github.com) should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over). Text can be bold, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).
Paragraph There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs. There should be whitespace between paragraphs.</description></item><item><title>c# 学习第一天</title><link>https://banksy10.github.io/test-c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://banksy10.github.io/test-c/</guid><description>.NET平台 c#是一种编程语言。可以开发基于.NET平台的应用{Java既是一种编程语言，也是一个平台 } .NET Framework框架是, italic, or strikethrough. Links should be blue with no underlines (unless hovered over).
Paragraph Blockquote &amp;gt; There should be no margin above this first sentence. &amp;gt; &amp;gt; Blockquotes should be a lighter gray with a gray border along the left side. &amp;gt; &amp;gt; There should be no margin below this final sentence. There should be no margin above this first sentence.
Blockquotes should be a lighter gray with a gray border along the left side.</description></item></channel></rss>